<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MOVIEBOX</string>
    <string name="bullet_train">
        Five assassins aboard a swiftly moving bullet train find out that their missions have something in common. Unlucky assassin Ladybug (Brad Pitt) is determined to do his job peacefully after one too many gigs has gone off the rails. Fate has other plans, however Ladybug\'s latest mission puts him on a collision course with lethal adversaries from around the globe all with connected, yet conflicting, objectives on the world\'s fastest train. The end of the line is just the beginning in this non stop thrill ride through modern day Japan. Experiencing unprecedented calmness thanks to newfound spiritual enlightenment, retired assassin Ladybug gets back in the game with a straightforward mission snatch an aluminium attache case from a speedy Shinkansen train bound for Kyoto, and return it to its owner in one piece. However, there\'s always a catch to great sounding deals. As five vicious hitmen vie for the same silver briefcase, hidden agendas get in the way, and everything that can go wrong will go wrong. Undoubtedly, Ladybug is a bad luck magnet. What awaits him at the end of the line is anyone\'s guess.
    </string>
    <string name="deadpool2">
        Foul mouthed mutant mercenary Wade Wilson (a.k.a. Deadpool) assembles a team of fellow mutant rogues to protect a young boy with supernatural abilities from the brutal, time traveling cyborg Cable. After losing Vanessa (Morena Baccarin), the love of his life, fourth wall breaking mercenary Wade Wilson, aka Deadpool (Ryan Reynolds), must assemble a team and protect a young mutant Russell Collins, aka Firefist (Julian Dennison), from Cable (Josh Brolin), a no nonsense, dangerous cyborg from the future, and must also learn the most important lesson of all to be part of a family again.
    </string>
    <string name="dune1">
        A noble family becomes embroiled in a war for control over the galaxy\'s most valuable asset while its heir becomes troubled by visions of a dark future. A mythic and emotionally charged hero\'s journey, Dune tells the story of Paul Atreides, a brilliant and gifted young man born into a great destiny beyond his understanding, who must travel to the most dangerous planet in the universe to ensure the future of his family and his people. As malevolent forces explode into conflict over the planet\'s exclusive supply of the most precious resource in existence a commodity capable of unlocking humanity\'s greatest potential only those who can conquer their fear will survive.
    </string>
    <string name="forrest_gump">
        The history of the United States from the 1950s to the 70s unfolds from the perspective of an Alabama man with an IQ of 75, who yearns to be reunited with his childhood sweetheart. Forrest Gump is a simple man with a low I.Q. but good intentions. He is running through childhood with his best and only friend Jenny. His mama teaches him the ways of life and leaves him to choose his destiny. Forrest joins the army for service in Vietnam, finding new friends called Dan and Bubba, he wins medals, creates a famous shrimp fishing fleet, inspires people to jog, starts a ping pong craze, creates the smiley, writes bumper stickers and songs, donates to people and meets the president several times. However, this is all irrelevant to Forrest who can only think of his childhood sweetheart Jenny Curran, who has messed up her life. Although in the end all he wants to prove is that anyone can love anyone.
    </string>
    <string name="free_guy">
        When Guy, a bank teller, learns that he is a non player character in a bloodthirsty, open world video game, he goes on to become the hero of the story and takes the responsibility of saving the world. In the extremely popular video game, Free City, a NPC named Guy learns the true nature of his existence when he meets the girl of his dreams, a human player. This player\'s interactions with Guy has massive affects on him, the game, and real world as they play it. Brimming with optimism and positive energy, single bank teller Guy has spent nearly all his uneventful life wishing he were one of the cool people wearing sunglasses people who run his town. But, one day, Guy has a chance encounter with mysterious Millie, the woman of his dreams, and just like that, he\'s on the brink of making an eye opening, life altering discovery. Now, to win her heart, all that Guy has to do is take control of his life, one step at a time. And then, out of the blue, Millie decides to drop a bombshell. However, is she telling the truth Above all, if life is nothing but a game, what will it take for ordinary Guy to level up and get the girl
    </string>
    <string name="oppenheimer">
        The story of American scientist J. Robert Oppenheimer and his role in the development of the atomic bomb. A dramatization of the life story of J. Robert Oppenheimer, the physicist who had a large hand in the development of the atomic bomb, thus helping end World War 2. We see his life from university days all the way to post WW2, where his fame saw him embroiled in political machinations.
    </string>
    <string name="the_adam_project">
        After accidentally crash landing in 2022, time traveling fighter pilot Adam Reed teams up with his 12 year old self for a mission to save the future. Adam Reed, age 12 and still grieving his father\'s sudden death the year before, walks into his garage one night to find a wounded pilot hiding there. This mysterious pilot turns out to be the older version of himself from the future, where time travel is in its infancy. He has risked everything to come back in time on a secret mission. Together they must embark on an adventure into the past to find their father, set things right, and save the world. As the three work together, both young and grown Adam come to terms with the loss of their father and have a chance to heal the wounds that have shaped them. Adding to the challenge of the mission, the two Adams discover that they really don\'t like each other much, and if they are to save the world, first they need to figure out how to get along.
    </string>
    <string name="the_batman">
        When a sadistic serial killer begins murdering key political figures in Gotham, Batman is forced to investigate the city\'s hidden corruption and question his family\'s involvement. Two years of nights have turned Bruce Wayne into a nocturnal animal. But as he continues to find his way as Gotham\'s dark knight Bruce is forced into a game of cat and mouse with his biggest threat so far, a manic killer known as The Riddler who is filled with rage and determined to expose the corrupt system whilst picking off all of Gotham\'s key political figures. Working with both established and new allies, Bruce must track down the killer and see him brought to justice, while investigating his father\'s true legacy and questioning the effect that he has had on Gotham so far as The Batman.
    </string>
    <string name="the_conjuring">
        Paranormal investigators Ed and Lorraine Warren work to help a family terrorized by a dark presence in their farmhouse. In 1971, Carolyn and Roger Perron move their family into a dilapidated Rhode Island farm house and soon strange things start happening around it with escalating nightmarish terror. In desperation, Carolyn contacts the noted paranormal investigators, Ed and Lorraine Warren, to examine the house. What the Warrens discover is a whole area steeped in a satanic haunting that is now targeting the Perron family wherever they go. To stop this evil, the Warrens will have to call upon all their skills and spiritual strength to defeat this spectral menace at its source that threatens to destroy everyone involved.
    </string>
    <string name="the_hangover">
        Three buddies wake up from a bachelor party in Las Vegas, with no memory of the previous night and the bachelor missing. They make their way around the city in order to find their friend before his wedding. Angelenos Doug Billings and Tracy Garner are about to get married. Two days before the wedding, the four men in the wedding party   Doug, Doug\'s two best buddies Phil Wenneck and Stu Price, and Tracy\'s brother Alan Garner   hop into Tracy\'s father\'s beloved Mercedes convertible for a 24 hour stag party to Las Vegas. Phil, a married high school teacher, has the same maturity level as his students when he\'s with his pals. Stu, a dentist, is worried about everything, especially what his controlling girlfriend Melissa thinks. Because she disapproves of traditional male bonding rituals, Stu has to lie to her about the stag, he telling her that they are going on a wine tasting tour in the Napa Valley. Regardless, he intends on eventually marrying her, against the advice and wishes of his friends. And Alan seems to be unaware of what are considered the social graces of the western world. The morning after their arrival in Las Vegas, they awaken in their hotel suite each with the worst hangover. None remembers what happened in the past twelve or so hours. The suite is in shambles. And certain things are in the suite that shouldn\'t be, and certain things that should be in the suite are missing. Probably the most important in the latter category is Doug. As Phil, Stu and Alan try to find Doug using only what little pieces of information they have at hand, they go on a journey of discovery of how certain things got into the suite and what happened to the missing items. However they are on a race for time as if they can\'t find Doug in the next few hours, they are going to have to explain to Tracy why they are not yet back in Los Angeles. And even worse, they may not find Doug at all before the wedding.
    </string>
</resources>